[
    {
        "question": "Which side of Niagara Falls has the largest falls - the US or Canadian side?",
        "answer": "Canadian"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the first four digits of Beverly Hill` zip code?",
        "answer": "9021"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has more volcanoes than any other?",
        "answer": "Indonesia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Toronto is on the shores of which Great Lake?",
        "answer": "Ontario"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river runs through Baghdad?",
        "answer": "Tigris"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of stone is Georgia`s Stone Mountain?",
        "answer": "Granite"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country would you find the port of Rosetta?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to The Willis Tower?",
        "answer": "Chicago"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to The CN Tower?",
        "answer": "Toronto"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the Westminster Clock Tower?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the Shukhov Tower?",
        "answer": "Moscow"
    },
    {
        "question": "South America`s Atacama Desert holds what distinction?",
        "answer": "Driest non-polar desert -- Although it is home to about one million people, it records less than 1 mm of rain every year."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only South American country to use the U.S. dollar as its official currency?",
        "answer": "Ecuador -- After a financial crisis in 2000, Ecuador switched from its currency to U.S. dollars due to citizen demand for dollars."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which river carved the Grand Canyon?",
        "answer": "Colorado River"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the majority of the Las Vegas Strip located?",
        "answer": "Paradise -- The majority of the 4.2-mile stretch of glittering lights is actually located in the neighboring town of Paradise."
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is home to the Gateway Arch?",
        "answer": "St. Louis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hells Canyon is located in which two US states?",
        "answer": "Idaho and Oregon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Oneida Lake is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to the twin cities of Benton Harbor and Saint Joseph?",
        "answer": "Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Albuquerque is located on the shores of what river?",
        "answer": "Rio Grande River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows along the northern border of Kentucky?",
        "answer": "Ohio River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Guggenheim museum?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Surrey town is famed for its salts?",
        "answer": "Epsom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country has Budapest as its capital?",
        "answer": "Hungary"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is Cornell University?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the principle language of Brazil?",
        "answer": "Portuguese "
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocean separates North America from Europe?",
        "answer": "Atlantic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you drive the Road to Hana?",
        "answer": "Maui, Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to Theodore Roosevelt National Park?",
        "answer": "North Dakota"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you see the Great Stalacpipe Organ?",
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Winchester Mystery House?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Sphinx Observatory located?",
        "answer": "Switzerland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to Olympic National Park?",
        "answer": "Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named `Nevsky Prospekt`?",
        "answer": "St. Petersburg"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named `Carnaby Street`?",
        "answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named `Biscayne Boulevard`?",
        "answer": "Miami"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named `La Rambla`?",
        "answer": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named `Nathan Road`?",
        "answer": "Hong Kong"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city would you find the most famous street named `Yonge Street`?",
        "answer": "Toronto"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Panama Canal connects the Gulf of Panama and which sea?",
        "answer": "Caribbean sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two oceans does the Panama Canal ultimately connect?",
        "answer": "Pacific and Atlantic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European city is served by Galileo Galilei Airport?",
        "answer": "Pisa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which German federal state surrounds the city-state of Berlin?",
        "answer": "Brandenburg"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is home to the longest street in the world?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Moho is an extinct genus of birds that were endemic to which island archipelago?",
        "answer": "Hawaiian Islands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the Republic of Nauru previously known as?",
        "answer": "Pleasant Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which continent would you find the Congo River?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ocean does the Congo River flow into?",
        "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean does the Congo River empty into?",
        "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Canada`s national anthem?",
        "answer": "O Canada"
    }
]